Guide to the Rice University athletic records, 1912-2010 (UA 155) UA 155
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Administrative, 1929-2002 (Boxes 11-45), 201958
  - Subseries F: Media Guides, 1950-2007, 202119
    - Football, 1985-1986, 202127 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Football, pre-season prospectus, 1986, 202126 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Football, 1987-1989, 202125 (Box 36, Folder 28-29)
    - Football, 1990, 1992, 202124 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Football, 1993-2004; Men's basketball, 1955-1994, 202123 (Box 37, Folder -)
    - Men's basketball, 1995-2006; Women's basketball, 1980-2006; Baseball, 1977-1988, 202122 (Box 38, Folder -)
    - Baseball, 1989-2007, 202121 (Box 39, Folder -)
    - Golf, 1975-2006, 202120 (Box 39, Folder 1-4)
  - Subseries G: Other administative files, clippings, 1930-2002, 201959
    - Admissions, 202118 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Advising, 1988-1990, 202117 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Athletic awards, 202116 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Budget plans and proposals, 1985-1990, 202115 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Holiday cards, undated, 202114 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Clippings, 1995-1996, 202113 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, 1998-1999, 202112 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 1999-2000, 202111 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 2000-2001, 202110 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - NCAA legislative assistance (Julie's notes), 202109 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Rice Intercollegiate Athletic Department, policies and procedure manual, 1983-1984, 202108 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Rice Owls sports news, 1989-1991, 202107 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Southwest Athletic Conference, meeting minutes, agendas, reports, 1969-1973, 202106 (Box 40, Folder 13-15)
    - Southwest Athletic Conference, meeting minutes, agendas, reports, 1974, 202105 (Box 40, Folder 16-17)
    - Speed City, 1992 edition, 202104 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Stadium chart, Astrodome, 202103 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Stadium charts, "New Stadium for Rice Institute.", 202102 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Stadiun charts, Summit and Rice Stadium, 202101 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Stadium seating inventory, season ticket allocation, 202100 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Stadium charts, tennis and gym, 202099 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Baseball photos, negatives1978-1982, undated, 202098 (Box 40, Folder 24-31)
    - Stadium, Jake Hess Tennis Stadium, 202097 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
    - Stadium, South end boxes, 202096 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Travel, 1989-1991, 202095 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Baseball, 1957, 202094 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Baseball, 1958, 202093 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Baseball, 1960, 202092 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Baseball scorebooks, 1960-61, 202091 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Baseball (Freshmand and Varsity), 1962, 202090 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Baseball (Varsity), 1963, 202089 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Baseball (Varsity) scorebook, 1966, 202088 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Baseball, 1974, 202087 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Baseball statistics, 1977-78, 1981-82, 202086 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Baseball, 1978, 202085 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Baseball games, 1979, 202084 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Baseball scorebook, 1979, 202083 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Baseball box scores, 1979, 202082 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Baseball, 1980, 202081 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Baseball, 1981, 202080 (Box 41, Folder 19-20)
    - Baseball, 1982, 202079 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Baseball scorebook, 1982, 202078 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Baseball statistics, 1982-83, 202077 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Baseball, 1983, 202076 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Baseball NCAA scorebook, 1983, 202075 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Baseball,1983, 202074 (Box 41, Folder 26-27)
    - Baseball,1984, 202073 (Box 41, Folder 28-30)
    - Baseball NCAA scorebooks,1984, 202072 (Box 41, Folder 31-32)
    - Baseball, 1985, 202071 (Box 41, Folder 33-34)
    - Baseball NCAA scorebook, 1985, 202070 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Baseball NCAA scorebook, 1985, 202069 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Baseball, 1986, 202068 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Baseball NCAA scorebook, 1986, 202067 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Baseball, 1987, 202066 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Baseball game notes, 1987, 202065 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Baseball, 1987, 202064 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - SWC Baseball notes, 1987-1989, 202063 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - SWC Baseball notes, 1988, 202062 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Baseball game notes, 1988, 202061 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Baseball box scores, 1988, 202060 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Baseball box scores, 1989, 202059 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Baseball "news and notes", 1989, 202058 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Baseball, 1990, 202057 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Baseball scorebook, 1991, 202056 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Baseball rosters and schedules, 1992, 202055 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Baseball statistics, 1992, 202054 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Sam Houston State baseball, 1992, 202053 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Nicholls State baseball, 1992, 202052 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Texas-Pan American baseball, 1992, 202051 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Texas baseball, 1992, 202050 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Southwest Texas State baseball, 1992, 202049 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Texas Tech baseball, 1992, 202048 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Houston baseball, 1992, 202047 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - McNeese State baseball, 1992, 202046 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - University of Mississippi baseball, 1992, 202045 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Baylor baseball, 1992, 202044 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Lamar baseball, 1992, 202043 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Clippings, 1994, 202042 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Baseball box scores, 1994, 202041 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Baseball news releases, 1994, 202040 (Box 42, Folder 30-31)
    - Official NCAA Baseball scorebook Rice Owls, 1994-1995, 202039 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Baseball statistics, 1995, 202038 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Baseball clippings, 1995, 202037 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Baseball statistics, 1995-96, 202036 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Baseball clippings, 1996, 202035 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Baseball college world series, 1996, 202034 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Baseball college world series logo, 1996, 202033 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Western Athletic Conference (WAC) Baseball, 1996, 202032 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Baseball scorebooks, 1996, 202031 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - Baseball stadium, 1999, 202030 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - 1930-31 Lettermen Awards, 202029 (Box 42a, Folder 1)
    - 1931-32 Lettermen Awards, 202028 (Box 42a, Folder 2)
    - 1932-33 Lettermen Awards, 202027 (Box 42a, Folder 2)
    - 1933-34 Lettermen Awards, 202026 (Box 42a, Folder 3)
    - 1934-35 Lettermen Awards, 202025 (Box 42a, Folder 4)
    - 1935-36 Lettermen Awards, 202024 (Box 42a, Folder 5)
    - 1936-37 Lettermen Awards, 202023 (Box 42a, Folder 6)
    - 1937-38 Lettermen Awards, 202022 (Box 42a, Folder 7)
    - 1938-39 Lettermen Awards, 202021 (Box 42a, Folder 8)
    - 1939-40 Lettermen Awards, 202020 (Box 42a, Folder 9)
    - 1940-41 Lettermen Awards, 202019 (Box 42a, Folder 10)
    - 1941-42 Lettermen Awards, 202018 (Box 42a, Folder 11)
    - 1942-43 Lettermen Awards, 202017 (Box 42a, Folder 12)
    - 1943-44 Lettermen Awards, 202016 (Box 42a, Folder 13)
    - 1944-45 Lettermen Awards, 202015 (Box 42a, Folder 14)
    - 1945-46 Lettermen Awards, 202014 (Box 42a, Folder 15)
    - 1946-47 Lettermen Awards, 202013 (Box 42a, Folder 16)
    - 1947-48 Lettermen Awards, 202012 (Box 42a, Folder 17)
    - 1948-49 Lettermen Awards, 202011 (Box 42a, Folder 18)
    - 1949-50 Lettermen Awards, 202010 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - 1950-51 Lettermen Awards, 202009 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - 1951-52 Lettermen Awards, 202008 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - 1952-53 Lettermen Awards, 202007 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - 1953-54 Lettermen Awards, 202006 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - 1954-55 Lettermen Awards, 202005 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - 1955-56 Lettermen Awards, 202004 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - 1956-57 Lettermen Awards, 202003 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - 1957-58 Lettermen Awards, 202002 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - 1958-59 Lettermen Awards, 202001 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - 1959-60 Lettermen Awards, 202000 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - 1960-61 Lettermen Awards, 201999 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - 1961-62 Lettermen Awards, 201998 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - 1962-63 Lettermen Awards, 201997 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - 1963-64 Lettermen Awards, 201996 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - 1964-65 Lettermen Awards, 201995 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - 1965-66 Lettermen Awards, 201994 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - 1966-67 Lettermen Awards, 201993 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - 1967-68 Lettermen Awards, 201992 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - 1968-69 Lettermen Awards, 201991 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - 1969-70 Lettermen Awards, 201990 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Administrative, 201989 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - B and G, 201988 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 201987 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Clippings Folder 2, 201986 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Decathlon Team, 201985 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - H. Malcolm Lovett, 201984 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Misc., 201983 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Owl Club, 201982 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Photos, 201981 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Recruiting Info, 201980 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Sports Illustrated, 201979 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Sprinkler Contract, 201978 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - 1953 Releases, 201977 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - 1960s, 201976 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Spring Sports 1970s, 201975 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - 1981-82 Budget, 201974 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - 1983-84 Budget, 201973 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - 1983-84 Sports News, 201972 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - 1985-86 Rice Owls, 201971 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - 1985-86 Rice Owls Folder 2, 201970 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Research, 201969 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - 1986 Rice Owls, 201968 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - 1986-87 Rice Owls, 201967 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - 1986-87 Rice Owls Folder 2, 201966 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - 1987 Concerts, 201965 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - 1989 W-A-M Meeting, 201964 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - 1992-93 Clips Folder A, 201963 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - 1992-93 Clips Folder B, 201962 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Academics and Athletics, 201961 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Academic All-America, 201960 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Series III: Rice Sports (see also Series I: Swimming records), 1941-2004 (Boxes 46-71), 201056
  - Subseries A: Baseball, 1984-1997 and undated, 201918
    - 1984 Media Guide, 201957 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - 1986, 201956 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - 1987, 201955 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - 1988, 201954 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - 1989, 201953 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - 1993, 201952 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Sports News 1981-93, 201951 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - 1997, 201950 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Applications received after closing date 4-19-91, 201949 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Head Baseball Coach Search 1991, 201948 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Holds for Wayne Graham, 201947 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - 1991 Recommendations for Applicants, 201946 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Bill Bethan, 201945 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Bill Bratcher, 201944 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Gary Cowan, 201943 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - John Edwards, 201942 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Jim Gattis, 201941 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Dave Gorrie, 201940 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Wayne Graham, 201939 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Elliot Johnson, 201938 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - James Keller, 201937 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Dub Kilgo, 201936 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Roy Kinnan, 201935 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Jim Lawler, 201934 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Gerald Lewis, 201933 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Charles Maiorana, 201932 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - David Moss, 201931 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Raynor Noble, 201930 (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - Rusty Pendergrass, 201929 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - Stephen Prentice, 201928 (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - Vern Ruhle, 201927 (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - Kurt Seibert, 201926 (Box 46, Folder 32)
    - Chris Smith, 201925 (Box 46, Folder 33)
    - Clint Welch, 201924 (Box 46, Folder 34)
    - Paul Wolf, 201923 (Box 46, Folder 35)
    - Clippings, 201922 (Box 46, Folder 36)
    - Grad House Confirmation, 201921 (Box 46, Folder 37)
    - Photos; folder 1 of 2, 201920 (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - Photos; folder 2 of 2, 201919 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - Subseries B: Basketball, 1957-1998, 201782
    - Certificates, 201917 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 201916 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Men's Basketball Photos, 201915 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Photos, 201914 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - 1957, 201913 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - 1958, 201912 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - 1959, 201911 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - 1960, 201910 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - 1960 Rice-Texas Cage Classic, 201909 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - 1961, 201908 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - 1962, 201907 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - 1963, 201906 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - 1964, 201905 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - 1968, 201904 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - 1969, 201903 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - 1970, 201902 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - 1972, 201901 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - 1973, 201900 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - 1974, 201899 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - 1975, 201898 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - 1977, 201897 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - 1978, 201896 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - 1979, 201895 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - 1980, 201894 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - 1981, 201893 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - 1982, 201892 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - 1983, 201891 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - 1984, 201890 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - 1985, 201889 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - 1985-86 Game Notes Rice Owls, 201888 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - 1986, 201887 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Women's Basketball 1988, 201886 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Men's Basketball 1988, 201885 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - 1989, 201884 (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - American Athletic Association of the Deaf 35th Annual National Basketball Tournament Houston, TX March 28-31, 1979, 201883 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Fifth Annual Golden Gate Invitational December 1981, 201882 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - 1984 Southwest Conference Basketball Championship, 201881 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - McIntire, Mary 1988-91 Continuing Studies, 201880 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - 1989, 201879 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Sterling McCall Toyota, 1989-90, 201878 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Coaching Staff Office remodeling, 1989-91, 201877 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - RICE OWLS Athletic New Bureau, Rice Men's Basketball News, 1989-1991, 201876 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Transfer students, 1989-92, 201875 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Women's Basketball 1989-1990, 201874 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - "Three Pointers" Booster Club, 1990-92, 201873 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Holmes, David 1990-93, 201872 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - SWC Committee information, 1991, 201871 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Basketball Southwest Conference, 1991, 201870 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Owl Club, restricted funds, 1991, 201869 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Fields of Dreams Foundation, 1991-93, 201868 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - National Invitation Tournament, 1991-94, 201867 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Texas Association of Basketball Coaches (TABC), 1991-94, 201866 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - "3-Pointers" Booster Club, 1992, 201865 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Japan Trip, 1992, 201864 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - NCAA Coaches information, 1992, 201863 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Coaching Position applications, 1992-93, 201862 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - "3-Pointers" Winner Circle, 1992-93, 201861 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - General news, correspondence, 1992-93, 201860 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Summer Camp, 1992-93, 201859 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - NCAA, 1992-94, 201858 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Coaches Clinic, 1992, 201857 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Furniture/Stationery, 1992, 201856 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Basketball breakfasts, 1992-93, 201855 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Men's Basketball 1992-93 Clippings, 201854 (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - Box scores, 1993, 201853 (Box 48, Folder 31)
    - Grades from Julie G., 1993, 201852 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    - High School Coaches, 1993, 201851 (Box 48, Folder 33)
    - High School Players, 1993, 201850 (Box 48, Folder 34)
    - NABC Issues Summit, Charlotte, NC, 1993, 201849 (Box 48, Folder 35)
    - National Invitational Tournament Preseason, 1993, 201848 (Box 48, Folder 36)
    - Scouting report companies, 1993, 201847 (Box 48, Folder 37)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs, 1993-94, 201846 (Box 48, Folder 38)
    - Managers, student coaches, 1993-94, 201845 (Box 48, Folder 39)
    - Players' File, 1993-94, 201844 (Box 48, Folder 40)
    - SWC Meetings, 1993-94, 201843 (Box 48, Folder 41)
    - Southwest Conference, 1993-94, 201842 (Box 48, Folder 42)
    - Southwest Conference Officials, 1993-94, 201841 (Box 48, Folder 43)
    - May, Bobby, and Barbara Tolar, 1993-94, 201840 (Box 48, Folder 44)
    - Coaching Position applicants, 1994, 201839 (Box 48, Folder 45)
    - Cousins, Bill "Men's Basketball notes", 1994, 201838 (Box 48, Folder 46)
    - National Association of Basketball Coaches (NABC), 1994, 201837 (Box 48, Folder 47)
    - NABC, Final Four, 1994, 201836 (Box 48, Folder 48)
    - Southwest Conference, spring meetings, 1994, 201835 (Box 48, Folder 49)
    - Andrews, Torrey, 201834 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Barcelona, Tim, 201833 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Bell, Hakim Ali, 201832 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Cooper, Michael Alan, 201831 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Daniels, Carl E., 201830 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Eubanks, Dajun, 201829 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Fuller, Kevin, 201828 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Gay, Alain, 201827 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Gentry, Charles, 201826 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Giacoletti, Ray, 201825 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Gilchrist, Andy, 201824 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Giovanine, Grey, 201823 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Girardi, Mike, 201822 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Hardy, Dana, 201821 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Hines, Greg, 201820 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Holmes, Richard, 201819 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Irving, Michael, 201818 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Johnson, Greg, 201817 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Kleine, Bill, 201816 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Maag, Chase, 201815 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Marshall, JT, 201814 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Matthiason, Magnus, 201813 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Mircea, Dr. Aurel E., 201812 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Mlachnik, Dave, 201811 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Moore, Marvin, 201810 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Murphy, Walter D., 201809 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Parker, Jay, 201808 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Pastner, Hal, 201807 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Peabody, Tom, 201806 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Price, Greg, 201805 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Robertson, Ronald, 201804 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Rourke, Kenneth, 201803 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Ruffcorn, Kevin, 201802 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Rupp, (President) George "Drug-free University" policy no. 323-91, 201801 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Schoettelkotte, Todd, 201800 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Scott, Brent, 201799 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Scott, Richard "Chip", 201798 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Stepp, Bart, 201797 (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - Strickland, Will, 201796 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - Tanner, D'Wayne, 201795 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - May, Bobby, Barbara Tolar, 201794 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - Tynes, Scott, 201793 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - Willie, David, 201792 (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - Youngkin, Glenn, 201791 (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - Agents, 201790 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs of Greater Houston, 201789 (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - Charity, 201788 (Box 49, Folder 47)
    - Christian Broadcasting Network (CBN) Summer Camp, 201787 (Box 49, Folder 48)
    - Bill Cousins, Sports Information, 201786 (Box 49, Folder 49)
    - General, 201785 (Box 49, Folder 50)
    - Owl Club, Jim Harris, John Greer, 201784 (Box 49, Folder 51)
    - Women's Basketball 1998, 201783 (Box 49, Folder 52)
  - Subseries C: Track, 1961-1998, 201416
    - 1961 Workouts, 201781 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - 1962 Practice Results, 201780 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - 1963 Practice Results, 201779 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - 1964 Practice Results, 201778 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - 1965 Workouts and Results, 201777 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - 1966 Practice Results, 201776 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - 1967 Workouts and Results, 201775 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - 1968 Spring Workouts, 201774 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Fall 1968 Workouts and Results, 201773 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Spring 1970 Workouts and Results, 201772 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - 1970 Fall Workouts and Results, 201771 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Spring 1971 Workouts and Results, 201770 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - XC 1971-72, 201769 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - XC 1972, 201768 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - XC Fall 1973, 201767 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - 1973 Workouts and Results, 201766 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - XC 1974, 201765 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - 1974 Spring Workouts, 201764 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - XC Spring 1975, 201763 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - XC 1975 Fall, 201762 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Rice Invitational XC 1975, 201761 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - XC Spring 1976, 201760 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - XC 1976 Fall, 201759 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - XC 1976, 201758 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Rice Invitational XC 1976, 201757 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - XC Spring 1977, 201756 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - XC 1977, 201755 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Rice Invitational 1977, 201754 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - XC Spring 1978, 201753 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - XC 1978, 201752 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Rice Invitational XC 1978, 201751 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - XC Spring 1979, 201750 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - XC Fall 1979, 201749 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - XC 1979, 201748 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Rice Invitational XC 1979, 201747 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - 1980 Spring, 201746 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - 1980 Fall Workouts, 201745 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - XC 1980, 201744 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Rice Invitational XC 1980, 201743 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - 1981 Fall Workouts, 201742 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - XC 1981, 201741 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Rice Invitational XC 1981, 201740 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - XC 1982, 201739 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - 1982 Rice Invitational, 201738 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - 1982 on SWCTCA, 201737 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - XC Spring 1983, 201736 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - XC Fall 1983, 201735 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - XC 1983, 201734 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - 1983 Bests, 201733 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Rice Invitational XC 1983, 201732 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - XC Spring 1984, 201731 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - XC 1984, 201730 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - 1984 Bests, 201729 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - 1984 Meets, 201728 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Rice Invitational XC 1984, 201727 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - 1984 TAC, 201726 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - 1985 Indoor Results, 201725 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - 1985-86 Results, 201724 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - XC 1985, 201723 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - 1985 Bests, 201722 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Rice Invitational XC 1985, 201721 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - XC 1986, 201720 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - 1986 Bests, 201719 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - 1986 NCAA, 201718 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - 1986 NCAA District VI, 201717 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - 1986 NCAA (Tucson), 201716 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Rice Invitational 1986, 201715 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - 1986 SWC, 201714 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - 1987 SWC indoor (Fort Worth), 201713 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - XC 1987-88, 201712 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - XC 1987, 201711 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - 1987 NCAA, 201710 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - 1987 NCAA (Baton Rouge), 201709 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - 1987 NCAA (Oklahoma City), 201708 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - 1987 Post World Indoor (Indianapolis), 201707 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - 1987 SWC, 201706 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - 1987 SWC Championships, 201705 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - XC 1988, 201704 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - 1988 NCAA, 201703 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - 1988 NCAA District VI, 201702 (Box 53, Folder 21)